http://www.tokn.com/privacy-policy/

Contact Information
This Privacy Statement describes how Thompson, O’Brien, Kemp & Nasuti, P.C. (“TOKN”) collects, uses, and discloses certain personal information obtained through our public web site at www.tokn.com. This Privacy Statement does not address information collection through other sources such as in-person seminars or an attorney’s personal contacts.
Personal Information Collection and Use
In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we ask for personally identifiable information from you, such as your name, company, e-mail address, phone number, and address (“Personal Information”). We request this information in order to correspond with you, to provide you with a subscription to a newsletter or publication, to notify you about events, or otherwise to respond to your requests or provide you with information that we consider may be of interest to you. Where applicable, we will differentiate between personal data fields that are optional and those that are mandatory to obtain the requested information.
If you receive a marketing e-mail from TOKN, you will be provided with an automated way to opt out (unsubscribe) from that particular communication or from all marketing e-mails sent by our Firm. Please follow the instructions on the e-mail you received. If you have received unwanted e-mail from our Firm, please forward a copy of that e-mail to info@tokn.com.
Please note that if you reply to a TOKN address in one of our marketing e-mails or otherwise send a communication to us, your communication will not create a lawyer-client relationship with us. Do not send us any information that you or anyone else considers to be confidential or secret unless we have first agreed to be your lawyers in that matter. Any information you send us before we agree to be your lawyers cannot be protected from disclosure.
Data Sharing
We may share Personal Information with our law firm for purposes of responding to your requests or otherwise as necessary for the purposes described above. We may also in limited circumstances share Personal Information with government authorities or others as required to protect the interests of the Firm or others, as necessary in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a portion of a business or real estate, or as required by applicable law or court order.
International Data Transfers
Our website is hosted on a web server in the United States. If you are located in a non-US jurisdiction, your provision of Personal Information or other access to our web sites constitutes your transfer of such data to the United States, a jurisdiction that may not provide a level of data protection equivalent to the laws in your home country.
Security Measures
TOKN maintains appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect the security of your Personal Information against the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or alteration.
Links to Other Web Sites
The privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Statement are for our website only. This we site may contain links to other sites. TOKN is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. If you link to or otherwise visit any other site, please review the privacy policies posted at that site.
Cookies and Passive Tracking
A “cookie” is an element of data that can be sent to your browser. Your browser may then store it on your system based on the preferences you have set on your browser. Cookies gather information about your operating system including, but not limited to, browser type, and Internet Protocol (IP) address. The TOKN website uses this information to analyze the traffic on our website, and better serve you when you return to our website. It is not our intention to use such information to personally identify a user. You have the option to configure your Internet browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Further, you have the option to block all cookies. Please note, however, that if you refuse or otherwise block cookies you may not be able to use all of the functionality available on the website.
Access and Correction
We provide individuals with access to their Personal Information where we believe appropriate, including in situations where you are entitled to access and review your Personal Information under applicable data protection and privacy laws.  If you wish to access or update the Personal Information you submit through our website, or to make any inquiries about the processing of such information, please contact us at privacy@tokn.com or write to us at the following address:  Thompson, O’Brien, Kemp & Nasuti, P.C., 40 Technology Pkwy S, #300, Peachtree Corners, GA 30092.
Revisions to this Privacy Statement
TOKN reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check the Privacy Statement frequently and particularly before you submit additional personal information via the Web Site. All revisions to this Privacy Statement will be posted on the website via a link from the homepage.  This Privacy Policy was last revised and effective November 13, 2018.
Practice GroupsBankruptcy
Corporate Law
Litigation
Local Government
Real Estate
Meet Our Dedicated Attorneys
J. Patrick O’Brien
View Profile
12.11.19
Get to Know Barry Smith Barry Smith is a vital member of our team. In fact, he is a valuable asset to every core practice group within TOKN. Barry has…
Adding An Adult Child To Home Deed
11.01.19
If you are considering adding your adult child to your home deed then consider these factors first. Often, I receive questions from clients asking if they should add their adult…
WE ARE GROWING… New Office in Savannah, Georgia
10.22.19
We are very excited to announce the opening of our new Savannah, Georgia office! Our Savannah, Georgia address is:2 E. Bryan Street, Suite 442Savannah, Georgia 31401 You may reach us…
